Stafford, Ronald B.; Papers apap217
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1974-2002; 9; 32.51 cubic ft.
  - Legislative Resolution Congratulating Mrs. L. Bullis on the Grand Occasion of her One Hundred Second Birthday, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 91)
  - An Act to Amend the Municipal Home Rule Law, in Relation to the Adoption of Certain Local Laws, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 92)
  - Legislative Resolution Honoring and Congratulating Dr. L. Bristol on the Occasion of his Relinquishing the Gavel of Authority of Grand Exalted Ruler of The Benevolent and Protective Oder of Elks, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 93)
  - Legislative Resolution Congratulating the City of Glens Falls, the Adirondack Red Wings Hockey Team and the Promoters of the Brand New Glens Falls Civic Center, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 94)
  - Concurrent Resolution Proposing an Amendment Permitting the Exchange of Certain Forest Preserve Land, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 95)
  - Legislative Resolution Urging Executive or Legislative Action to Have the Crime of Arson Classified as a Class I Crime, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 96)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Use of University or College Degrees, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 97)
  - Definition of Institution of Higher Education with Respect to Parents and Students Savings Plans, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 98)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Approved Programs for the Purposes of Determining a Students Eligibility for Certain Academic Awards, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 99)
  - Eliminate State Funding for Legal Representation of Indigent Inmates for Certain Legal Matters, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 100)
  - Establishing a Lien for Real Estate Brokerage Commissions, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 101)
  - An Act to Repeal Section 11-101 of General Obligations Law, Relating to the So-Called "Dram Shop Act" and Terminating the Effect of all Rules and Regulations Promulgated Incidental Thereto, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 102)
  - Civil Service Exams for Certain Positions in the Department of Correctional Services, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 103)
  - Require State Funds to be Placed in Interest Bearing Accounts, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 104)
  - Providing a Credit Against Person Income Taxes for the Cost of Wood Heating Fuels During Certain Taxable Years, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 105)
  - Legislative Approval of the Adirondack Park Master Plan and Individual Plans, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 106)
  - An Act to Amend the Agriculture and Markets Law, in Relation to the Referendum Advisory Committee with Respect to the Dairy Industry, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 107)
  - An Act to Incorporate the Maine Permanent Firemen's Exempt Benevolent Association and Providing for its Functions, Powers and Duties, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 108)
  - An Act to Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to Abandonment, Alteration, or Changes in use of Highway, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 109)
  - An Act to Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law and the Military Law, in Relation to the Application and Payment for Certain Service Credit, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 110)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to fee authorization and the effective date of imposition thereof, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 111)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to the Automatic Stay of the Enforcement of Judgments or Orders Against the State or Political Subdivisions, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 112)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Advance Payment of Fees of an Attorney who is also a Trustees of an Express Trust, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 113)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Time for Publication of Summons, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 114)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to the Deposition of a Person Authorized to Practice Medicine, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 115)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Definition of Foreign State in Article 53, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 116)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Remembering Section 811-A relating to Fixed Fees of Sheriff of Rockland County, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 117)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Omissions on Appeal, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 118)
  - An Act to Amend the Facilities Development Corporation Act, in Relation to the Design and Construction of Municipal Facilities and Repealing Sections 8-b and 14-b thereof, 1979 (Box 5 (9-Legislation), Folder 119)
  - An Act to Amend the County Law, in Relation to State Aid to Counties for Salaries of District Attorneys, and making an Appropriation therefor, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Tuition Assistance Program, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to the Appointment of a Receiver, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Notice of Motion for Protective Order, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Junior Archery Licenses and Bow Hunting Stamps, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to Adirondack Park Agency Approval of other State Agency Projects, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Minimum Appointment of Public Moneys to School Districts, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 7-8)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to the Number of Peremptory Challenges, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - An Act to Amend the Real Property Tax Law, in Relation to Certain State Lands Subject to Taxation for All Purposes, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Establishment of Foreign Trade Zones by the Clinton County Area Development Corporation, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - An Act to Amend the Penal Law and Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Restitution or Reparation to a Victim for the Loss or Damage Caused by an Offense, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to the Exemption of Articles of Clothing from Sales and Use Taxes, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Definition of the Term Eligible Youth for the Purposes of Youthful Offender Adjudication and the Penal Law, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Credit for Income Tax Imposed by the Provinces of Quebec and Ontario, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Athletic Training License, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 16-19)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Allowing Vendors a Reimbursement Fee for Collection of Sales and Use of Taxes, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Addition of a New Article 99 to the CPLR entitled Construction Contract Actions and Special Proceedings Against Public Corporations, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - An Act to Amend the Town Law, in Relation to Allowing for the Adoption of the Town Meeting Concept by Certain Towns, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - Creation of the Bureau of Crime Prevention within the Division of Criminal Justice Services, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to the Illegal Taking of Wildlife, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Providing an Additional Employment Incentive Tax Credit Under Article 9-A Such Law for the Employment of Youth, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Appropriation to the DEC to Provide Services for the Improvement of Fish and Wildlife Habitat and to Provide Access for Fish and Wildlife Recreation, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to the Jurisdiction of Justice Courts to Issue a Warrant of Arrest and the Procedure After Arrest in the Event the Court is not Available, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Administration Cost Allowance with Respect to Tuition Assistance Program Awards and Student Loans, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - Appropriation to the Commissioner of Education for Establishing a "New York State Legislative Talent Scholarship Program" for Gifted and Talented High School Juniors, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Permitting Service of a Supplemental Bill of Particulars Upon a Party Containing Claims for Continuing Special Damages, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Appeals and Repealing Certain Provisions thereof Relating thereto, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to the Appearance of Corporations in Certain Actions, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Tolling the Statute of Limitations, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to the Continuation of a Stay, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Contracts with Certain Independent Colleges and Universities, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - Appropriation to Meet Part of the Operating Expense of the Admission Referral and Information Center of the Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - An Act to Amend the Municipal Home Rule Law, in Relation to the Adoption of Certain Local Laws, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Authorizing Clinton County to Apply for and Accept a Grant for the Establishment of Foreign Trade Zones and Subzones, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - Appropriation for the Purpose of Continuing the Operations of Certain Fish Hatcheries in New York State, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Excluding Moneys Received as Federal Military Retirement Payments from the Tax on Personal Income, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Including Mobile Homes in the Homestead Exemption, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Requiring an Affidavit for Certain Appeals, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to the Taking of an Appeal, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - An Act to Repeal Rule Twenty-Two Hundred Sixteen of the Civil Practice Law and Rules Relating to Appearance and Default on Motions, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to the Period of Time a Defendant may be held in Custody on a Felony or Misdemeanor Complaint, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - An Act to Amend the Social Services Law, in Relation to Liability of Relatives to Support Children, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - Designation a Portion of the State Highway System as "The Frank A. Moore Memorial Highway", 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - An Act to Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law, in Relation to Certain Disabilities of Uniformed Personnel in Institutions Under the Jurisdiction of the Department of Correctional Services, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - An Act to Amend the Labor Law, in Relation to the Requirement of Unemployment Insurance for those Persons Enrolled in a Community Agency Program Pursuant to the Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - An Act to Amend the Town Law, in Relation to Appropriations for Veterans' Organizations, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Licensing of Hearing Aid Dispensers, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - Gathering Dead Timber from the State Forest Lands, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - An Act to Amend the Real Property Tax, in Relation to Notice of Increased Assessments in Certain Towns, Cities and Counties, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 53)
  - Limiting the Amount of Money that can be Recovered against a Municipal Corporation for Personal Injuries and Authorize the Review of Verdicts, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 54)
  - An Act to Amend the Penal Law, in Relation to Reasons for Minimum Sentences, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 55)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Certain Exemptions from Sales and Use Taxes, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 56)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Certain Exemptions from Sales and Use Taxes, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 57)
  - An Act to Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to Providing for Increased Payments and Minimum Payments by the State to Municipalities in Contracts for the Removal of Snow and Ice, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 58)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Falconry Hunting by the Use of Raptors, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 59)
  - An Act to Amend the Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to Requiring Inspection of Floor Area in Annual Inspection of Motor Vehicles, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 60)
  - Personal Income Tax Exemption for Retired Members of the Armed Forces, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 61)
  - Disposal of Dead Wood in the Adirondack Park, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - Legislative Review of Proposed State Agency Rules, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 63)
  - Exempting Home Heating Fuels from the Sales and Compensating Use Tax in Certain Cases, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 64)
  - An Act to Legalize, Validate, Ratify, and Confirm Certain Actions of the Town Board of the Village of Keeseville, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 65)
  - An Act to Amend the Social Services Law, in Relation to Responsibility of Parents for Medical Assistance Received by Child Between the Ages of 18 and 21 years Living Away from Home, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 66)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Indemnification and Defense of Officers and Employees at the Board of Higher Education in the City of New York, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 67)
  - An Act to Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to State Highways in Clinton County, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 68)
  - An Act to Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law, in Relation to Retirement of Certain Members in the Uniformed Personnel of the Department of Correction, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 69)
  - Ban Discharge of Public Sewage into Lake George, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 70-71)
  - An Act to Amend the General Municipal Law and the Highway Law, in Relation to Time Limitations in Wrongful Death Actions Brought Against Municipal Corporations, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 72)
  - An Act to Amend the Real Property Tax Law, in Relation to an Incorrect Entry on an Assessment of Tax Roll, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 73)
  - An Act to Amend the Labor Law, in Relation to Valid Original Claims Under the Unemployment Insurance Law, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 74)
  - An Act to Amend the Real Property Tax Law, in Relation to Correction of Assessment and Tax Rolls, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 75)
  - Authorize the Town of Massena to Convey Lands to the Diagnostics, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 76)
  - Authorize the Town of Horicon to Grant and Expend Money for the Support, Maintenance, and Capital Improvement of the Heintzelman Library and Renaming such library to be the Cultural Education Center, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 77)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Refunds of Tax on Motor Fuel for School Buses, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 78)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to the Adirondack Park Agency, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 79)
  - Allow the Carrying of Pistols and Revolvers while Hunting Deer during an Archery or Muzzle-Loading Season, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 80)
  - Authorizing the Use of Bicycles on the New York World War Veterans Memorial Highway in Essex County, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 81)
  - Designating a Portion of the State Highway System as "The Adirondack Turnpike", 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 82)
  - Legislative Resolution Creating a Special Joint Legislative Task Force to Study the Implementation of the Adirondack Park Agency Act and to Report the Results of its Studies to the Legislature, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 83)
  - An Act to Amend the Retirement and Social Security Law and the Education Law, in Relation to Supplemental Retirement Allowances, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 84)
  - An Act to Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to Certain Specifications for Town Highways Located within the Adirondack Park, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 85)
  - An Act to Amend the Judiciary Law, in Relation to the County Seal of Franklin County, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 86)
  - An Act to Amend the Judiciary Law, in Relation to Disqualification of Jurors, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 87)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to an Order of Recognizance or Bail, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 88)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Authorizing the Temporary Separation of a Deliberating Jury, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 89)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Quasi in Rem Jurisdiction and Related Provisions of Article 3, and Repealing Certain Provisions Relating Thereto, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 90)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Material Which by Law Cannot be Sold by the Sheriff Pursuant to Judgment Execution, 1979 (Box 6 (9-Legislation), Folder 91)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to the Addition of Parties, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Personal Service of a Summons on a Natural Person, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - An Act to Amend the Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to Axle Load Limits upon Certain Vehicles, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Establishing a New Discovery Procedure, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Persons Causing Death or Injury by Discharge of a Firearm or Long Bow, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Service Law, in Relation to the Health Insurance Plan, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Authorizing the Peru Central School District to Refund Federal Monies Received Pursuant to PL 8774 in Excess of the Amount Budgeted, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - An Act Making an Appropriation for the Planning of a Tourist Information Center in the Vicinity of Warrensburg, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - An Act to Amend the Penal Law, in Relation to the State Division of Parole, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - An Act to Amend the Public Officers Law, in Relation to the Indemnification of Officers and Employees of the State, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Appropriation to the State Board of Equalization and Assessment to Conduct a Study of the Economic Impact of the Adirondack Land Use and Development Plan, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - Addition of a New Article 99 to the CPLR entitled Construction Contract Actions and Special Proceedings Against Public Corporations, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Members on the Board of the Teachers' Retirement System, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - An Act to Amend the Commerce Law, in Relation to Economic Assessments in Certain Cases, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Certain Modifications Reducing Federal Adjusted Gross Income on State Personal Income Tax Returns, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - An Act to Amend the General Obligations Law, in Relation to the Duty to Keep Premises Safe for Certain Uses, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Private Sector Capital Improvements for Concession Facilities at State Owned Ski Centers, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Require the State to Reimburse a Local Social Services District for the Amount Expended by it for Home Relief, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Authorize the Commissioner of General Services to Convey Certain Realty to Clarkson College, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - An Act to Amend the Labor Law, in Relation to the Minimum Wage Payable to Employees of Amusement or Recreational Establishments, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to Affirmative Defenses, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Legislative Resolution Urging the United State Olympic Committee to Designate Lake Placid as the Permanent Training Site for United State Athletes Competing in Winter Olympic Games, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to the Joinder of Crimes in Indictment of Juvenile Offender, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Conditional Examination of Witnesses, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to a Hearing upon a Motion to Suppress Evidence, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Payment of Bonuses to Korean and Vietnam War Veterans, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - Concurrent Resolution Proposing an Amendment in Relation to Woodland Improvement of Wildlife Habitat, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - Concurrent Resolution Proposing an Amendment in Relation to Appropriation Bills, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - Concurrent Resolution Proposing an Amendment in Relation to Permitting the Credit of the State to be Extended for the Purpose of Promoting the Tourist Industry, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to County Awards for Professional Education in Medicine, Dentistry or Optometry or Veterinary Medicine, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - Establishing a Credit on Wood Furnace Installations Against the Franchise Tax on Business Corporations, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - Creating the Adirondack Park Tax District and Establishing its Powers and Duties, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to the Adirondack Park Agency, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Payment of Bonuses to Korean and Vietnam War Veterans, 1979 (Box 7 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)